# Tyra Paukei

Oklahoma City, OK tpaukei@gmail.com +1 813 860 4160

With experience in customer service and sales, I strive to be focused and empathetic to those around me. With efficiency in making sure customers are comfortable and reassured. Also able to upkeep with fast paced and stressful environments, I intend to be the calm amongst the storm in chaotic atmospheres!

I have advanced computer skills, typing skills, and a determined mindset. Whether it's team based work or extremely independent, I do my best to adapt to the situation and make the best out of it. I have been trained heavily on empathy, handling stressful situations, and creating a relaxed atmosphere for customers.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

## Work Experience

#### Safety/Dispatch Agent

Airbnb Sutherland - Oklahoma City, OK April 2022 to Present

The Safety team within Airbnb coordinates between taking high-risk calls and collecting important information to help the users while.

We are trained to handle the most extreme situations in order to keep the in danger user calm, reassured, and leveled to be able to help us, help them get them to a safe and comfortable location as quickly as possible.

We also take on safety-related cases with our users, speaking directly with the user and keeping track of their data and the status of the case.

The most important value is being able to identify our users needs with efficiency. Maintaining a strict work schedule and routine coaching that go over our metrics to create goals on how best to improve.

#### **Captioning Agent**

Caption Call - Oklahoma City, OK October 2021 to April 2022

Trained agent in using dictation to caption phone calls verbatim for the hard of hearing and elderly. Having to use typing skills as well. Working out of a VDI program and statistics based attendance.

#### Sales Class

Events by Keko - Oklahoma City, OK January 2018 to February 2018

A Marketing Firm where we learned advanced sales skill and marketing techniques. Demonstrating those techniques through selling clientele products in retail marketplaces.

#### **Food Service Worker**

Taco Bueno - Guthrie, OK July 2017 to November 2017

A line cook in charge of creating and making food orders in an extremely fast paced environment. Time management skills and customer service.

#### Education

## **High school**

#### Skills

- Athlete (5 years)
- Typing
- Statistics
- Food Service
- Sales
- · Computer Skills
- Microsoft Outlook

#### Assessments

### **Work motivation — Proficient**

March 2020

Level of motivation and discipline applied toward work

Full results: Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

#### Additional Information

I am an extremely quick learner to all types of elements of jobs. My people skills are impeccable, and relatable. Communicating with a team is preferred, and being a helping hand will always be a priority.